<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>010423_Welcome</title>
      <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, friends and new visitors, to my cooking blog! I&amp;rsquo;m so glad you&amp;rsquo;re here.
This website is a collection of recipes that I have personally tried and enjoyed, found on Youtube and the internet. I love to cook and eat a wide variety of cuisines, from American to Indian and everything in between. Some of my all-time favorite recipes that I&amp;rsquo;ve come across include:
Baked Salmon: This simple yet delicious recipe is a go-to for me when I want a healthy, protein-packed meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010723 Nutrition_fitness_lifestyle_guide</title>
      <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/nutrition_fitness_lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/nutrition_fitness_lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
Welcome to my guide on how to improve your nutrition, fitness, and overall well-being! In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing some tips and strategies that I&amp;rsquo;ve found helpful in my own journey towards optimal health. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re just starting out on your health journey or you&amp;rsquo;re looking to fine-tune your routine, I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll find something useful here.
I encourage you to take these tips and try them out for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010823_Benefits_of_shorter_flights</title>
      <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/benefits-of-short-flights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/benefits-of-short-flights/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to India or somewhere accross the world and wondering how to get there? As an Indian living in the US, I have to make this journey quite often to visit friends, family and also conduct some business. While it may be tempting to just book a long haul flight and get it over with, I&amp;rsquo;ve found that breaking up the journey with shorter flights can actually be a much more enjoyable and rewarding experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010923_The_search_for_golden_ghee</title>
      <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/golden-ghee-nutrition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/golden-ghee-nutrition/</guid>
      <description>As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
For as long as I can remember, I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a quest for the perfect golden ghee, and let me tell you, it&amp;rsquo;s been a wild ride. Starting from the early years, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried every butter under the sun, from ready-made ghee to name brand grassfed butters, fancy imported Indian, Australian, and European brands to your conventional cow grocery store stick, let&amp;rsquo;s just say I&amp;rsquo;ve had some&amp;hellip;disappointments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>011023_Fiber_and_probiotics_work_together</title>
      <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/why-you-should-eat-fiber-and-probiotics-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/why-you-should-eat-fiber-and-probiotics-together/</guid>
      <description>As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
When I first started my health and nutrition journey in 2012, I really focused on eating more vegetables, salads and fiber. I noticed that keeping my fiber intake high, I had a much easier time maintaining my body composition. Fortunately, I grew up in an Indian household and daal was one of the staple foods. Lentils and beans are a great source of fiber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>011123_Downs_Thompson_paradox</title>
      <link>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/downs_thompson_paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blazingstarz.xyz/posts/downs_thompson_paradox/</guid>
      <description>Why aren&amp;rsquo;t all cities built for cyclists and where should we go? As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
As a bicycle enthusiast, I am very drawn to the idea of living in a city that has excelent pedestrian and cycling infrastructure. Living in America, I am missing out on some of the safe cycling paths that pedestrian focused cities have. In all of the cities I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in, most of the protected bike lanes were just simple painted lines without any real dividers to keep cars out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
