<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bread on Recipies</title>
    <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/tags/bread/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bread on Recipies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/tags/bread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bao_bun</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/bao_bun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/bao_bun/</guid>
      <description>Recipe adapted from Johanna Ware, Smallwares, Portland, OR
Yield: 12 to 14 buns Prep Time: 20 minutes, plus proofing time Cook Time: 8 minutes Total Time: 28 minutes, plus proofing time
Ingredients: ⅔ cup warm water 2 teaspoons instant yeast 2 tablespoons sugar 1 tablespoon canola oil 1¼ cups bread flour, plus more for if needed 1 teaspoon kosher salt ¼ teaspoon baking soda Directions: In a small bowl, whisk together the water, yeast and sugar until the yeast dissolves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic_naan</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/garlic_naan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/garlic_naan/</guid>
      <description>Restaurant Style Garlic Naan Soft and Buttery Homemade Garlic Naan - just like the one from your favorite Indian restaurant! Enjoy it with your favorite curry!
PREP TIME 15 mins
COOK TIME 20 mins
RESTING TIME 1 hr 30 mins
TOTAL TIME 2 hrs 5 mins
SERVINGS 8 naan
CALORIES 295 kcal
INGREDIENTS 3.25 cups +3-4 tablepoons all purpose flour 423 grams + 27-36 grams), also known as maida 1 teaspoon salt 1 cup water lukewarm, 8 oz 1 tablespoon sugar 2 teaspoons active dry yeast 1/3 cup milk lukewarm 2 tablespoons plain yogurt 3 tablespoons oil I used vegetable 2 large garlic cloves grated nigella seeds/kalonji Garlic Butter, to brush on naan 3 tablespoons butter I used unsalted 3 tablespoons chopped cilantro 2 teaspoons minced garlic INSTRUCTIONS In a bowl whisk together 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick_focaccia</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/quick_focaccia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/quick_focaccia/</guid>
      <description>Foccacia bread is amazing with soups, as a side dish or appetizer, but my favourite thing about it is that it&amp;rsquo;s so,so delicious just on it&amp;rsquo;s own. And this recipe is really quick and easy and ready in just 60 minutes! Try it and you&amp;rsquo;ll love the infinite flavor possiblilties of this foccacia bread!
Ingredients: 1 ¾ Cup AP Flour (215 grams) ½ tsp Sugar (2 grams) ½ tsp Salt (3 grams) 1 ½ tsp Quick-Rise Instant Yeast (4.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
