<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipies</title>
    <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Recipies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Badhakopir_ghonto_cabbage</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/badhakopir_ghonto_cabbage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/badhakopir_ghonto_cabbage/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 15 g Mustard oil 1 piece Dried red chilli (whole) 1 piece Bay leaf (whole) 1 piece Cardamom (whole) 1 piece Clove (whole) 1 piece Cinnamon (whole) 2 g (or ¼ tsp) Cumin seeds 400 g Cabbage (cut into thin shreds, 2 mm wide) 100 g Potatoes (diced; 3 cm cubes) 50 g Peas (shelled) 30 g Tomatoes (diced) 75 g Prawns (optional; shelled and deveined) 20 g Ginger paste 2 g Cumin powder 1 g Coriander powder 3 g Turmeric powder 1 g Red chilli powder 10 g Salt 25 g Sugar 4 g Ghee ¼ tsp Garam masala powder 2 pieces Green chillies (slit) Method PART I—CUTTING THE CABBAGE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bao_bun</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/bao_bun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/bao_bun/</guid>
      <description>Recipe adapted from Johanna Ware, Smallwares, Portland, OR
Yield: 12 to 14 buns Prep Time: 20 minutes, plus proofing time Cook Time: 8 minutes Total Time: 28 minutes, plus proofing time
Ingredients: ⅔ cup warm water 2 teaspoons instant yeast 2 tablespoons sugar 1 tablespoon canola oil 1¼ cups bread flour, plus more for if needed 1 teaspoon kosher salt ¼ teaspoon baking soda Directions: In a small bowl, whisk together the water, yeast and sugar until the yeast dissolves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef_stroganoff</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/beef_stroganoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/beef_stroganoff/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound ground beef Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper One 10-ounce package white mushrooms, halved or quartered if large 1 tablespoon extra-virgin olive oil 1/2 teaspoon paprika 3 cloves garlic, finely chopped 1 carrot, cut into 1/4-inch dice 1 small onion, chopped 1 tablespoon tomato paste One 15-ounce can low-sodium beef broth 1 tablespoon Worcestershire sauce 2 cups dried penne pasta 2 ounces cream cheese, at room temperature 1/4 cup sour cream 3 tablespoons chopped fresh chives 3 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley leaves Directions: Heat a large nonstick skillet over medium-high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bolognese</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/bolognese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/bolognese/</guid>
      <description>Ingedients 1 yellow onion, rough chopped
1 carrot, rough chopped
1 stalk celery, rough chopped
1 tablespoon neutral oil
1 pound 80/20 ground beef
2 cloves garlic, minced
1/2 cup dry white wine or dry vermouth
1 – 15 ounce can crushed tomatoes
3 tablespoons tomato paste
2 cups beef broth
1 bay leaf
2 teaspoons dried oregano
1 teaspoon red pepper flakes
3 tablespoons balsamic vinegar
1 1/2 cups milk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast_burrito</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/breakfast_burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/breakfast_burrito/</guid>
      <description>INGREDIENTS: Bacon, Egg, &amp;amp; Cheese Burrito:
3 Tbsp (42 g) Unsalted Butter
8 Eggs
Salt
Pepper
6-8 Slices of Thick Bacon (optionally chopped)
Grated Cheddar
Pico:
1 Large Red Tomato, diced
1 Jalapeno, diced
1/2 Sweet Onion, finely diced
A handful of Cilantro, chopped
1 lime, juice &amp;amp; zest
Olive Oil
Salt
Pepper
Hash Browns (optional):
2 large Russet Potatoes, peeled and grated
Oil (or butter)
Steak &amp;amp; Cheese Burrito Ingredients</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast_sandwhiches</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/breakfast_sandwhiches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/breakfast_sandwhiches/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 bagel, toasted or grilled
1 egg, over easy or sunny side up…or if you must: scrambled
1 slice American cheese (or whatever works for you)
2 tablespoons Bacon &amp;amp; Onion Jam, see recipe
2 sliced crispy bacon
1 tablespoon mayo
1/2 tablespoon mustard
Directions Add Bacon Jam to bottom bagel
While egg is cooking, add cheese so it can start melting
Add mayo &amp;amp; mustard to top bagel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cacio_e_pepe</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/cacio_e_pepe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/cacio_e_pepe/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 tablespoons (60ml) extra-virgin olive oil, divided
1 teaspoon coarsely ground black pepper, to taste
Kosher salt, to taste
1/2 pound (225g) spaghetti
2 tablespoons (30g) unsalted butter
2 ounces Pecorino Romano cheese (about 1 cup; 55g), very finely grated on a Microplane or the smallest holes of a box grater, plus more for serving
Directions Heat 3 tablespoons olive oil and about a teaspoon of black pepper in a medium skillet over medium-low heat until ingredients are fragrant and pepper is barely starting to sizzle, about 1 minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbonara</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/carbonara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/carbonara/</guid>
      <description>INGREDIENTS Yield: 4 servings
Salt 2large eggs and 2 large yolks, room temperature 1ounce (about ⅓ packed cup) grated pecorino Romano, plus additional for serving 1ounce (about ⅓ packed cup) grated Parmesan Coarsely ground black pepper 1tablespoon olive oil 3½ounces of slab guanciale (see recipe), pancetta or bacon, sliced into pieces about ¼ inch thick by ⅓ inch square 12ounces spaghetti (about ¾ box) Instructions Step 1
Place a large pot of lightly salted water (no more than 1 tablespoon salt) over high heat, and bring to a boil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ceasar_salad</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/ceasar_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/ceasar_salad/</guid>
      <description>INGREDIENTS: 6 cloves garlic
3 anchovy filets
Salt to taste
2 egg yolks
Juice of 1.5 large lemons
1 heaping Tbsp (18g) dijon
1.25 cup 300ml vegetable oil
3/4 cup grated parmigiano
Pepper to taste
Garlic bread Croutons
Leaves
INSTRUCTIONS: Method:
Start by smashing the garlic cloves, sprinkle with kosher salt, and finely chop using the rolling chop method. Chop, gather, chop, gather, and occasionally smear with a knife. Continue this process for 3-5 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken_tikka_massala</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/chicken_tikka_masala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/chicken_tikka_masala/</guid>
      <description>INGREDIENTS: Tikka Paste:
1 Tbsp (4g) coriander seeds
1/2 (1g) tsp cumin
1 Tbsp (7g) garam masala
1 tsp (3g) turmeric
7 cloves garlic
1 2inch piece ginger
1-2 fresno chilies depending on size
1/4cup (60ml) water
2 Tbsp (30ml) oil
Marinated Chicken:
1 cup (225g) yogurt
2 lbs chicken
2 Tbsp (26g) of tikka paste
2 tsp (7g) kosher salt
The Sauce:
1 28 oz can whole peeled tomatoes, blended strained (cook the water out)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastfood_burgers</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/fast_food_burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/fast_food_burger/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: Ground Beef (80/20) Salt Pepper Avocado Oil Lettuce Tomato Hamburger Buns Ketchup Mustard Frank&amp;rsquo;s red hot sauce American Cheese Instructions: Preheat your grill or stovetop grill pan to medium-high heat. You want it nice and hot so the burgers get a good sear.
Divide the ground beef into 4 equal portions and shape into patties. Sprinkle each patty with a little bit of salt and pepper on both sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh_pasta</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/fresh_pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/fresh_pasta/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 large eggs, beaten to blend 2 cups all-purpose flour 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 teaspoon kosher salt Preparation Mix eggs, flour, oil, and salt in the bowl of a stand mixer with your hands until a shaggy dough forms. Knead with dough hook until dough is smooth and elastic, about 10 minutes. Cover dough with cloth bowl cover and let rest at least 30 minutes. Cut and roll as desired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic_naan</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/garlic_naan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/garlic_naan/</guid>
      <description>Restaurant Style Garlic Naan Soft and Buttery Homemade Garlic Naan - just like the one from your favorite Indian restaurant! Enjoy it with your favorite curry!
PREP TIME 15 mins
COOK TIME 20 mins
RESTING TIME 1 hr 30 mins
TOTAL TIME 2 hrs 5 mins
SERVINGS 8 naan
CALORIES 295 kcal
INGREDIENTS 3.25 cups +3-4 tablepoons all purpose flour 423 grams + 27-36 grams), also known as maida 1 teaspoon salt 1 cup water lukewarm, 8 oz 1 tablespoon sugar 2 teaspoons active dry yeast 1/3 cup milk lukewarm 2 tablespoons plain yogurt 3 tablespoons oil I used vegetable 2 large garlic cloves grated nigella seeds/kalonji Garlic Butter, to brush on naan 3 tablespoons butter I used unsalted 3 tablespoons chopped cilantro 2 teaspoons minced garlic INSTRUCTIONS In a bowl whisk together 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ilish_mach</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/ilish_mach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/ilish_mach/</guid>
      <description>Here are two preparations of ilish mach. My favorite is Sorse Ilish Mach (Mustard Hilsha Fish)&amp;ndash;the mustard oil gives it a spicy and pungent flavor.
Ingredients: Sorse Ilish Mach 2 tbsp mustard seeds 1 tbsp black mustard seeds ½ cup water ½ tsp salt 2 ½ tbsp mustard oil ¼ tsp kalojire/kalonji 4-5 green chilies ¼ tsp turmeric ½ tsp red chili 5 ilish pieces ¼ cup coconut milk Lebu Ilish Mach 7 ilish mach pieces ¼ cup onion paste 1 tsp garlic-ginger paste 1 tsp green chili paste ½ tsp red chili ½ tsp cumin powder 1 tsp salt 2 tsp lime juice 2 tbsp cooking oil 4 medium onion Instructions for sorse ilish mach: Soak mustard seeds in water for 30 minutes Blend the soaked mustard seeds and green chilies with salt Set aside the mustard mixture Drizzle mustard oil in pan with kalojire and green chilies Stir for a minute before adding turmeric and red chilies Place ilish mach on pan and cook on low heat Pour the mustard mixture over the ilish mach Cook for 10 minutes Pour coconut milk Ready to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamb_curry</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/lamb_curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/lamb_curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 3 lb. lamb 2 tsp salt ½ cup yogurt ¼ cup cooking oil ¼ cup mustard oil 2 bay leaves ½ tsp pepper 2 black cardamom 5 cardamom 6 cloves 3 cinnamon sticks 3 cups sliced onion 1 tbsp ginger paste 1 tbsp garlic paste 3.5 cups hot water 2 tbsp Kashmiri chili 1 tsp fennel powder ½ tsp ginger powder Instructions: Marinate the lamb cuts with salt and yogurt for an hour Add cooking oil in a large pot along with mustard oil, bay leaves, pepper, black cardamom, green cardamom, cloves and cinnamon sticks Fry until fragrant for about a minute Add sliced onion and fry until brown Add the marinated lamb, ginger and garlic paste Saute for 10 minutes Pour hot water and cook for 45 minutes on medium-low heat with lid on Mix Kashmiri chili in water and pour it over the lamb dish for color and flavor Add fennel powder, ginger powder and cook for another 10 minutes with lid on Garnish with fresh coriander before serving Ready to Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemon_rice</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/lemon_rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/lemon_rice/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Rice - 1/2 cup Water To Boil Rice - 1 cup water Oil - 1 tbsp Salt To Taste Red Chili Whole - 2 no. Turmeric Powder - 1/2 tsp Curry Leaves - 6 to 7 Coriander Leaves for garnishing Urad Dal (Black split lentils without cover) - 1/2 tbsp Chana Dal (Bengal Gram) - 1/2 tbsp Peanuts - 12 to 15 Mustard Seeds - 1 tsp Lemon Juice - 1 tbsp Ginger Chopped - 1/2 tbsp Directions First rinse and soak rice for 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masoor_dal</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/masoor_dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/masoor_dal/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 3 tbsp cooking oil 4 garlic cloves ½ cup onion ½ tsp salt ¾ tsp turmeric 1 ½ cup masoor dal ½ cup green bell pepper ½ cup yellow bell pepper 4 cups hot water ¾ tsp salt 5-6 green chilies 1 medium tomato ¾ tsp roasted cumin 2 tbsp fresh coriander Instructions: Add cooking oil in a large pot along with sliced garlic, onion, salt to taste, and turmeric Stir in masoor dal that has been soaked for a minimum of 30 minutes Add green and yellow bell pepper Pour hot water Salt to taste Add green chilies, tomato pieces and roasted cumin Garnish with fresh coriander Ready to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar_paneer</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/matar_paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/matar_paneer/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 400-gram paneer 2 tbsp cooking oil 1 large chopped red onion ½ inch sliced ginger 2 garlic cloves 2 medium chopped tomato 2 green chilies 1 tsp cumin seeds 1 tsp red chili powder 1 tsp coriander powder ½ tsp turmeric 1 ½ cup green peas 1 cup water 1 tsp garam masala 4 tbsp chopped coriander Instructions: Cut the paneer into small cubes In a pan, sauté chopped onion, ginger, garlic, green chilies, and tomatoes until soft Remove from heat and puree using an electric hand blender and set aside Using the same pan, drizzle a bit of cooking oil for tempering cumin seeds Once the cumin seeds are fragrant, add red chili powder, coriander powder, turmeric, and the puree mixture Sauté for 7-8 minutes and add salt and water Cook for 4 minutes on low heat with lid on Add the cubed paneer, green peas and water Cook for 7 minutes on medium heat with lid on Remove lid and sprinkle garam masala Garnish with fresh chopped coriander Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/pizza/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 500 grams (4 ¼c) bread flour 16 grams (2 tsp) fine sea salt
1 gram (¼ tsp) active dry yeast
350 grams or 1 ½ cups of water
Directions In a large bowl, whisk together the bread flour, salt, and yeast.
Slowly add the water, and mix with a wooden spoon just to combine. Once the mixture is moistened, lightly flour a countertop or large cutting board and remove the dough from the bowl with lightly oiled or wet hands (to discourage sticking).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick_focaccia</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/quick_focaccia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/quick_focaccia/</guid>
      <description>Foccacia bread is amazing with soups, as a side dish or appetizer, but my favourite thing about it is that it&amp;rsquo;s so,so delicious just on it&amp;rsquo;s own. And this recipe is really quick and easy and ready in just 60 minutes! Try it and you&amp;rsquo;ll love the infinite flavor possiblilties of this foccacia bread!
Ingredients: 1 ¾ Cup AP Flour (215 grams) ½ tsp Sugar (2 grams) ½ tsp Salt (3 grams) 1 ½ tsp Quick-Rise Instant Yeast (4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short_rib_pappardelle</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/short_rib_pappardelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/short_rib_pappardelle/</guid>
      <description>Short Ribs with Pappardelle Beef short ribs are braised in a tomato red wine sauce with fresh thyme until the meat falls off the bone and tossed with pappardelle ribbons and plenty of Parmigiano Reggiano cheese.
Ingredients 10 3-4&amp;quot; bone-in short ribs about 3-4 pounds 2 teaspoons kosher salt plus more to taste 1/2 teaspoon black pepper plus more to taste 1 tablespoon olive oil 2 medium carrots diced 1 medium onion diced 2 cloves garlic sliced 3 ounces tomato paste 2 cups dry red wine chianti, cabernet, etc 1 28 ounce can plum tomatoes hand crushed or blender pulsed 1 large bay leaf 2 tablespoons fresh thyme 1 pound pappardelle 1 cup reserved pasta water will most likely not need all of it 1/2 cup Parmigiano Reggiano grated, for finishing Instructions Preheat oven to 300f and move racks to make enough room to accommodate a large Dutch oven pot in the middle of the oven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp_curry</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/shrimp_curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/shrimp_curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 ¾ cups coconut 1 ½ cups hot water 500 grams prawn ½ tsp salt ¼ tsp turmeric ½ tsp red chili 1 medium onion 1 bay leaf 3 green chilies 1 tsp ginger paste 1 medium tomato ¾ tsp salt 1 tbsp tomato paste 1 tsp coriander ½ tsp turmeric ½ tsp red chili ½ tsp garam masala 1 ¼ cups coconut milk ¾ tsp roasted cumin 1 tbsp fresh coriander Instructions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp_ramen</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/shrimp_ramen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/shrimp_ramen/</guid>
      <description>You wish you had this ramen in college.
YIELDS: 1
PREP TIME: 0 HOURS 10 MINS
TOTAL TIME: 0 HOURS 30 MINS
INGREDIENTS: 3 packages instant ramen, flavor pack discarded 1 tbsp. vegetable oil 1 lb. shrimp kosher salt Freshly cracked black pepper 1 tbsp. sesame oil 2 garlic cloves, minced 1 tsp. minced ginger 1/2 c. soy sauce 1/4 c. brown sugar Juice of 1 lime 2 tsp. sriracha 1 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steam_boiled_eggs</title>
      <link>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/steam_boiled_eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipies-cedu.onrender.com/recipies/steam_boiled_eggs/</guid>
      <description>The best, fastest, easiest-to-peel, and most energy efficient method I&amp;rsquo;ve found is to boil an inch or so of water in the bottom of a saucepan or wok. Add the eggs straight from your fridge (the water doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to cover them). Cover with a lid and boil/steam them 3 minutes for extremely soft, 4-5 minutes for soft, 6-7 minutes for medium, and 9-12 minutes for hard. Let them cool naturally or in an ice bath.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
