<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>favorites on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/tags/favorites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in favorites on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/tags/favorites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ceasar_salad</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/ceasar_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/ceasar_salad/</guid>
      <description>INGREDIENTS: 6 cloves garlic
3 anchovy filets
Salt to taste
2 egg yolks
Juice of 1.5 large lemons
1 heaping Tbsp (18g) dijon
1.25 cup 300ml vegetable oil
3/4 cup grated parmigiano
Pepper to taste
Garlic bread Croutons
Leaves
INSTRUCTIONS: Method:
Start by smashing the garlic cloves, sprinkle with kosher salt, and finely chop using the rolling chop method. Chop, gather, chop, gather, and occasionally smear with a knife. Continue this process for 3-5 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic_naan</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/garlic_naan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/garlic_naan/</guid>
      <description>Restaurant Style Garlic Naan Soft and Buttery Homemade Garlic Naan - just like the one from your favorite Indian restaurant! Enjoy it with your favorite curry!
PREP TIME 15 mins
COOK TIME 20 mins
RESTING TIME 1 hr 30 mins
TOTAL TIME 2 hrs 5 mins
SERVINGS 8 naan
CALORIES 295 kcal
INGREDIENTS 3.25 cups +3-4 tablepoons all purpose flour 423 grams + 27-36 grams), also known as maida 1 teaspoon salt 1 cup water lukewarm, 8 oz 1 tablespoon sugar 2 teaspoons active dry yeast 1/3 cup milk lukewarm 2 tablespoons plain yogurt 3 tablespoons oil I used vegetable 2 large garlic cloves grated nigella seeds/kalonji Garlic Butter, to brush on naan 3 tablespoons butter I used unsalted 3 tablespoons chopped cilantro 2 teaspoons minced garlic INSTRUCTIONS In a bowl whisk together 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ilish_mach</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/ilish_mach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/ilish_mach/</guid>
      <description>Here are two preparations of ilish mach. My favorite is Sorse Ilish Mach (Mustard Hilsha Fish)&amp;ndash;the mustard oil gives it a spicy and pungent flavor.
Ingredients: Sorse Ilish Mach 2 tbsp mustard seeds 1 tbsp black mustard seeds ½ cup water ½ tsp salt 2 ½ tbsp mustard oil ¼ tsp kalojire/kalonji 4-5 green chilies ¼ tsp turmeric ½ tsp red chili 5 ilish pieces ¼ cup coconut milk Lebu Ilish Mach 7 ilish mach pieces ¼ cup onion paste 1 tsp garlic-ginger paste 1 tsp green chili paste ½ tsp red chili ½ tsp cumin powder 1 tsp salt 2 tsp lime juice 2 tbsp cooking oil 4 medium onion Instructions for sorse ilish mach: Soak mustard seeds in water for 30 minutes Blend the soaked mustard seeds and green chilies with salt Set aside the mustard mixture Drizzle mustard oil in pan with kalojire and green chilies Stir for a minute before adding turmeric and red chilies Place ilish mach on pan and cook on low heat Pour the mustard mixture over the ilish mach Cook for 10 minutes Pour coconut milk Ready to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamb_curry</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/lamb_curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/lamb_curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 3 lb. lamb 2 tsp salt ½ cup yogurt ¼ cup cooking oil ¼ cup mustard oil 2 bay leaves ½ tsp pepper 2 black cardamom 5 cardamom 6 cloves 3 cinnamon sticks 3 cups sliced onion 1 tbsp ginger paste 1 tbsp garlic paste 3.5 cups hot water 2 tbsp Kashmiri chili 1 tsp fennel powder ½ tsp ginger powder Instructions: Marinate the lamb cuts with salt and yogurt for an hour Add cooking oil in a large pot along with mustard oil, bay leaves, pepper, black cardamom, green cardamom, cloves and cinnamon sticks Fry until fragrant for about a minute Add sliced onion and fry until brown Add the marinated lamb, ginger and garlic paste Saute for 10 minutes Pour hot water and cook for 45 minutes on medium-low heat with lid on Mix Kashmiri chili in water and pour it over the lamb dish for color and flavor Add fennel powder, ginger powder and cook for another 10 minutes with lid on Garnish with fresh coriander before serving Ready to Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masoor_dal</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/masoor_dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/masoor_dal/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 3 tbsp cooking oil 4 garlic cloves ½ cup onion ½ tsp salt ¾ tsp turmeric 1 ½ cup masoor dal ½ cup green bell pepper ½ cup yellow bell pepper 4 cups hot water ¾ tsp salt 5-6 green chilies 1 medium tomato ¾ tsp roasted cumin 2 tbsp fresh coriander Instructions: Add cooking oil in a large pot along with sliced garlic, onion, salt to taste, and turmeric Stir in masoor dal that has been soaked for a minimum of 30 minutes Add green and yellow bell pepper Pour hot water Salt to taste Add green chilies, tomato pieces and roasted cumin Garnish with fresh coriander Ready to enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar_paneer</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/matar_paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/matar_paneer/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 400-gram paneer 2 tbsp cooking oil 1 large chopped red onion ½ inch sliced ginger 2 garlic cloves 2 medium chopped tomato 2 green chilies 1 tsp cumin seeds 1 tsp red chili powder 1 tsp coriander powder ½ tsp turmeric 1 ½ cup green peas 1 cup water 1 tsp garam masala 4 tbsp chopped coriander Instructions: Cut the paneer into small cubes In a pan, sauté chopped onion, ginger, garlic, green chilies, and tomatoes until soft Remove from heat and puree using an electric hand blender and set aside Using the same pan, drizzle a bit of cooking oil for tempering cumin seeds Once the cumin seeds are fragrant, add red chili powder, coriander powder, turmeric, and the puree mixture Sauté for 7-8 minutes and add salt and water Cook for 4 minutes on low heat with lid on Add the cubed paneer, green peas and water Cook for 7 minutes on medium heat with lid on Remove lid and sprinkle garam masala Garnish with fresh chopped coriander Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick_focaccia</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/quick_focaccia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/quick_focaccia/</guid>
      <description>Foccacia bread is amazing with soups, as a side dish or appetizer, but my favourite thing about it is that it&amp;rsquo;s so,so delicious just on it&amp;rsquo;s own. And this recipe is really quick and easy and ready in just 60 minutes! Try it and you&amp;rsquo;ll love the infinite flavor possiblilties of this foccacia bread!
Ingredients: 1 ¾ Cup AP Flour (215 grams) ½ tsp Sugar (2 grams) ½ tsp Salt (3 grams) 1 ½ tsp Quick-Rise Instant Yeast (4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp_curry</title>
      <link>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/shrimp_curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recipes-73zj.onrender.com/recipes/shrimp_curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 ¾ cups coconut 1 ½ cups hot water 500 grams prawn ½ tsp salt ¼ tsp turmeric ½ tsp red chili 1 medium onion 1 bay leaf 3 green chilies 1 tsp ginger paste 1 medium tomato ¾ tsp salt 1 tbsp tomato paste 1 tsp coriander ½ tsp turmeric ½ tsp red chili ½ tsp garam masala 1 ¼ cups coconut milk ¾ tsp roasted cumin 1 tbsp fresh coriander Instructions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
